我要分功劳
I want credit for it.
不论你得到什么好处 我都要分一杯羹
Whatever you get, I want credit.
随便啦
Whatever.
- Thiessen先生 是你负责报道 犹太教堂那起爆炸吗? - 没错
Mr. Thiessen, you covered the bombing at the Oak Lawn synagogue?
据你观察此次爆炸和那次很类似?
- That's right. - And your opinion is that this bomb was very similar to that one?
几乎一模一样
Identical.
这两起案件中 爆炸装置 都是置于金属容器盒中
In both cases, the device was fashioned from a metal canister,
内部密集排放着硝酸  镍炸药
densely packed with hydrazine nitrate explosive and a simple,
由简单远程控制的回路操控
remote-triggered circuit.
但这个的引爆机制 和犹太教堂那次不同?
But this utilized a different triggering mechanism than the synagogue bombing?
不是 两者完全一致
It was identical.